to load up your
fundraising odds of success
is that it gives
the confidence If
the only has one
who's showing interest they're
like everything is hinged
on this one VC
Yeah it's like super
tunnel vision Super tunnel
vision desperate like live
or die kind situation
then the interaction between
that then the VC
will be like hey
is this founder actually
you know do people
actually want this Do
market forces support the
success of this company
Right They may not
say that I smell
desperation I should go
away You it's not
like that It's more
like they see that
And then they get
a that if I'm
the one backing it
the founder is not
gonna have enough money
to build a big
business You know and
even though I have
full conviction if nobody
else has conviction down
the line like this
is dead if you
see customers and and
whatever all in line
makes you yeah sure